<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</title>
    <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:10:23 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Covid Information</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/covid_information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:10:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/covid_information/</guid>
      <description>It is with great regret to inform you that I have been tested positive for COVID-19. For logistics purpose, I have created this post to list out key testing results and key contacts for your references. Some information has been redacted for privacy purposes.
Key Testing Results  Negative LFD result on 21/3 (Monday) afternoon. Mild symptom (coughing) developed on 22/3 (Tuesday) evening. A LFD test was done later that night and had negative result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MandI Jan26 Sigma Algebra</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mandi-jan26-sigma-algebra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 17:08:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mandi-jan26-sigma-algebra/</guid>
      <description>Summary  We have done previous exercise on semi-norm. Facts about $\sigma$-algebra  Uncountable intersection of $\sigma$-algebra is also a $\sigma$-algebra. That is why it makes sense to talk about &amp;ldquo;the smallest $\sigma$-algebra&amp;rdquo; containing certain subset of power set. To prove $\sigma(C) \subseteq \mathcal{F}$ you show that $C$ is contained in $\mathcal{F}$.    Exercise  Make sure you have read the proof of Carathedory extension theorem and the notions of null set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MathWiki Catchup 20/1</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mathwiki_jan-20-meeting-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 09:23:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mathwiki_jan-20-meeting-presentation/</guid>
      <description>The following is the agenda for the MathWiki catchup on 20/1/2022 (Thursday) 5pm on Microsoft Teams.
Participants:
 Amir (MathSoc President) Samuel (MathSoc Webmaster) Thomas (ImperialWiki Cofounder) Luc (ImperialWiki Student Partner) David (ImperialWiki Student Partner)  Agenda
 Updates on MathWiki website Proposed development Preparation of Student-Staff Committee (SSC) and other discussions with faculty members Google Analytics setup  Updates on MathWiki website Users  See Google Analytics (restricted access) Promotional emails were sent on 29th December (launch), 10th January (Week 1 email), 18th January (Week 2 email) Year distribution (based on email address)  Year 1: 55 (1/4 of cohort) Year 2: 73 (1/3 of cohort) Year 3: 47 (1/4 of cohort) Year 4: 38   Only 11 responses for the survey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;I Week 3 - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mandi-jan-20-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 09:07:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mandi-jan-20-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Follow up of lectures  Formalisation of Riemann (Darboux) Integral: the upper and lower Darboux sum is defined as  $$U(f) = \inf_\mathcal{P} U(f,\mathcal{P}), \quad L(f) = \sup_\mathcal{P} L(f,\mathcal{P})$$ where
$$U(f,\mathcal{P} = (x_i)_{i=0}^n) = \sum _{i=0}^{n-1} \left( \sup _{x \in [x_i, x _{i+1})} f(x) \right) (x _{i+1} - x_i)$$
$$L(f,\mathcal{P} = (x_i)_{i=0}^n) = \sum _{i=0}^{n-1} \left( \inf _{x \in [x_i, x _{i+1})} f(x) \right) (x _{i+1} - x_i)$$
 Incompleteness of $L^p$ space induced by Riemann Integral, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measure and Integration Study Group</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/measure-and-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:10:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/measure-and-integration/</guid>
      <description>Objective This is a trial study group as a follow up of the lectures of the course MATH50006 Lebesgue Measure and Integration (Imperial login required.)
Logistics Venue: Math Learning Centre (MLC, Huxley 414), Huxley Building, Imperial Time: 9.30am - 11.00am every Wednesday. Content: discussion of materials from the Tuesday lecture. Materials: See the relevant MathWiki page. (Imperial login required.)
Timetable  Week 3 (19/1) - Introduction, Function Spaces Week 4 (26/1) - Axioms of measure Week 5 (2/2) - Construction of measure I Week 6 (9/2) - Construction of measure II and Convergence almost everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March Weekly plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mar21-weekly-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:09:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mar21-weekly-plan/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Week 10 (6-12/3) Academic  Optimisation FYP:  Week 11 (13-19/3) Academic  Advanced Analysis: FYP:  Week 12 (20-26/3): Catch-up Week Week 13 (27/3-2/4): Personal branding week Week 14 (3/4-9/4) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February Weekly plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/feb21-weekly-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:01:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/feb21-weekly-plan/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Week 6 (6-12/2) 6/2 (Sunday) - Service and Interview  Sunday service CDT Random Systems (Imperial) interview Preparation for StatML interview  7/2 (Monday) - Interview  StatML interview Optimisation lecture MathWiki Preparation  8/2 (Tuesday)  Summer: enquiries for extending  9/2 (Wednesday)  Measure and Integration - Measurable sets and completeness, measure-determining set. FYP: Catchup Optimisation week 4/5 - day 1  10/2 (Thursday)  Optimisation week 4/5 - day 2 CU: Hub and Post-hub run CYF meeting  11/2 (Friday)  Optimisation week 4/5 - day 3 FYP: Density Estimation / Literature / Planning Sunday devotion planning CYF: BMT Planning  12/2 (Saturday)  Advanced Analysis: week 4/5 CYF  Week 7 (13-19/2): Catch-up, CU Events Week 13/2 (Sunday)  Mother&amp;rsquo;s birthday Bible study Badminton Planning exercises  14/2 (Monday)  Optimisation: lecture and coursework  15/2 (Tuesday) 16/2 (Wednesday)  Sunrise ride RailSoc tube challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYF Jan 16 Chit Chat</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-jan-16-chit-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:39:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-jan-16-chit-chat/</guid>
      <description>Quick notes from a discussion with CYF friends during the fellowship on 16/1/2021. I have just finished my Dynamics of Games homework and have been exhausted, so I decided to listen and I enjoy that so much. I am also glad that Yanni share my website to others.
 Jocelyn: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about deadair. (Although &amp;ldquo;introverts are happy if extroverts take over&amp;rdquo;.) Joseph: Go beyond being silent and try to respond to others sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January Weekly Plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan21-weekly-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 01:01:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan21-weekly-plan/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Week 5 (30/1-5/2): 30/1 (Sunday) - Church day  Morning: Sunday devotion and worship Afternoon: Worship practice Night: Interview preparation and mock interview  31/1 (Monday)  Sport: Running Optimisation: Follow up on development of relevant MathWiki page. Preparation of interview  1/2 (Tuesday) - Interview Day 2/2 (Wednesday) - MathWiki and Project Day  M&amp;amp;I Study Group MathWiki: Student Partners launch meeting FYP: Catchup with advisors  3/2 (Thursday)  Advanced Analysis: Lecture Interview: Preparation for StatML interview Christian Union: Hub CYF Meeting CU Mark Drama Publicity MathSoc Website Day 1  4/2 (Friday)  Prayer breakfast MathSoc Website Day 1 Preparation for StatML interview  5/2 (Saturday) - CYF and RailSoc Catchup  Morning: Bible Study Afternoon: CYF Night: Preparation for StatML interview  Past Week Week 2 (9-15/1): Dynamics of Games catch up Academic:  Dynamics of Games Coursework Optimisation: Slater&amp;rsquo;s condition, KKT condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Devotion</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/sunday-devotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:37:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/sunday-devotion/</guid>
      <description>Objective This is a trial devotion session to encourage CYF members developing habits of morning devotion. We will be reading 1 John every Sunday before the main service. It would be expanded if there are good outcomes.
Logistics Venue: McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in Hammersmith Broadway Time: 8.30am - 9.15am every Sunday. Content: discussion of prescribed materials and catchup. We will be reading 1 John.
Timetable 16/1 (Samuel) - Chapter 1  What is the word of life (v2)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jan 8 Meeting Minutes</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:19:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Decision after discussion Bible Study  Resume Sunday devotional breakfast: 1 John Resume daily bible reading:  Minor prophets Thessalonians Jeremiah and Lamentations Titus Philemon Ezekiel    Worship  Best training of musicians are to let them have more experience. Emphasis on communication among leaders and musicians.  Other Activities  Table football Music  Improvement for next time  Agenda too long! I have left my home in a rush so everything is in a mess!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branding</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:49:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/branding/</guid>
      <description>General Branding By week 5  Converting IG to public account and setup closed friends Design logo for website  Brand development week  Academic history: drawn from various personal statement Redesign webpage to make it more mobile friendly.  Leadership Interview Season 1 (Spring term election) By week 7:
 Invite leaders from different communities (e.g. MathSoc, CYF, CU, ICRTS, Wiki Initiatives) to talk about their passion and key to successful leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Outreach</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:23:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic-outreach/</guid>
      <description>Promotion of mathematics is divided into three main programmes: Integrated study group and MathWiki, MathSoc engagement and general outreach
Integrated study group and MathWiki Forming study group  ACTION: Elect as class representative of two courses I am taking, inviting people to contribute in MathWiki. ACTION: Deciding regular time of going over problem sheets / coursework  MathWiki Bear in mind this is not the priority for personal development.
Intermediate development:  By week 4:  20/1 Meeting between Amir and Thomas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Study Plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:03:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic/</guid>
      <description>My committment  3 days of FYP work each week 2 days per 2 week for normal academic work: Advanced Analysis, Optimisation See here for tentative schedule.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christianity</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/christianity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 01:17:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/christianity/</guid>
      <description>There are mainly two ways I am involved in outreaching as a christian - fellowship (Cantonese Youth Fellowship CYF) and Imperial College Christian Union (ICCU). However due to workload I will be gradually reducing my engagement in ICCU.
Cantonese Youth Fellowship As the vice-president of the CYF committee, I am responsible for facilitating President work and coordinating among other committees and participants. During the first term, I organised the freshers&#39; events and provided pastoral supports to the participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYF Early Jan Meetings</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-early-jan-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:38:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-early-jan-meetings/</guid>
      <description>The following is a summary for two meetings of CYF, happening on 30/12/2021 (Thursday) and 6/1/2022 (Wednesday). Both meetings are happening in Zoom.
Committee: Justin (President), Samuel (Vice-President), Vera (Vice-President de-facto, worship and music), Cherry (pastoral), Thomas (secretary), Chung (evangelism and outreach)
Covid Arrangement  Many CYF participants caught Covid after the gathering on 26/12/2021 (Sunday), and we have prayed for their recoveries. CYF is turning online. CYF will resume normal no later than February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masterplan Kickoff Meeting</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:40:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting/</guid>
      <description>The following is the agenda for the kickoff on 8/1/2022 (Saturday). Participants are reminded to take Covid test (LFD/PCR) 48 hours before attending. We are meeting 6pm at the foyer of Gabor Hall.
Three courses  Starter: Tomato soup Main: Spaghetti Carbonara Assorted vegetable Dessert: Ice Cream Snacks are provided  Discussion Lifestyle  regular exercise - how to sustain? designing easier meals  Academic Development  overview of coursework materials - what do you want to achieve?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 11:05:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/vision/</guid>
      <description>The following contents are taken from a discussion with my mother on 6/1/2022 (Thursday).
Basic Principles  Reflect on the expected achievements of plans everyday as a way to keep us going Start brainstorming with big direction, then set up easy (small) targets following the direction. It is easy to get lost: think about the example of Peter walking on the sea, and how Jesus responded when Peter hesitated. (Matthew 14:22-33, Bible) Successful planning involves lots of research and discussions Mind your language Be flexible, &amp;ldquo;be water my friend&amp;rdquo; (Bruce Lee)  Basic elements of a plan  knowledge skill habit (usually 21 days or 49 days) attitude  How to seek advice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:46:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>Healthier Lifestyle Regular Exercise Objectives:  Using prayer and exercise to boost my energy level at the start of the day. Enjoying sense of achievement after each workout Build partnership by doing workout with friends Contribute to improvement in resilience and singing techniques.  Goals:  Punctuality:  Monday night: Running, chest and leg Tuesday morning: Abs/Cores Wednesday morning: Leg/Chest Thursday morning: Running, Biceps and Triceps   Running: &amp;gt; 60 minutes with the speed of 10km/h within 3 months (TBC) Cycling: (TBC) Bicep/Tricep: (TBC) Back: (TBC) Core: (TBC) Chest: (TBC) Abs: (TBC) Leg: (TBC)  How to maintain  Weekly review with partners (TBC)  Healthy Diets Sleeping Time Spritual Growth (Bible Reading) Finance </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Page</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:58:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to masterplan 2022 The masterplan 2022 is an integration of various ambitious plans, outlined for personal development and fulfillment of duties in various communities. The main goal of the plan is to develop a healtheir lifestyle, have major breakthrough in academic development and make contributions to the development of various communities.
Categories  Personal Lifestyle Academic Academic Outreach Christianity Personal Branding  Pushing This is the key phrase of publishing the webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
