<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</title>
    <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 11:05:56 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 11:05:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/vision/</guid>
      <description>The following contents are taken from a discussion with my mother on 6/1/2022 (Thursday).
Basic Principles  Reflect on the expected achievements of plans everyday as a way to keep us going Start brainstorming with big direction, then set up easy (small) targets following the direction. It is easy to get lost: think about the example of Peter walking on the sea, and how Jesus responded when Peter hesitated. (Matthew 14:22-33, Bible) Successful planning involves lots of research and discussions Mind your language Be flexible, &amp;ldquo;be water my friend&amp;rdquo; (Bruce Lee)  Basic elements of a plan  knowledge skill habit (usually 21 days or 49 days) attitude  How to seek advice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:46:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>Healthier Lifestyle Regular Exercise Objectives:  Using prayer and exercise to boost my energy level at the start of the day. Enjoying sense of achievement after each workout Build partnership by doing workout with friends Contribute to improvement in resilience and singing techniques.  Goals:  Punctuality:  Monday night: Running, chest and leg Tuesday morning: Abs/Cores Wednesday morning: Leg/Chest Thursday morning: Running, Biceps and Triceps   Running: &amp;gt; 60 minutes with the speed of 10km/h within 3 months (TBC) Cycling: (TBC) Bicep/Tricep: (TBC) Back: (TBC) Core: (TBC) Chest: (TBC) Abs: (TBC) Leg: (TBC)  How to maintain  Weekly review with partners (TBC)  Healthy Diets Sleeping Time Spritual Growth (Bible Reading) Finance </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Page</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:58:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to masterplan 2022 The masterplan 2022 is an integration of various ambitious plans, outlined for personal development and fulfillment of duties in various communities. The main goal of the plan is to develop a healtheir lifestyle, have major breakthrough in academic development and make contributions to the development of various communities.
Categories  Personal Lifestyle Personal Academic Academic Outreach Branding Leadership  </description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
