<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Christian on Samuel Lam&#39;s Blogs</title>
    <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/categories/christian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christian on Samuel Lam&#39;s Blogs</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:07:15 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/categories/christian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Miscellaneous Entries</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/misc_review_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:07:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/misc_review_2022/</guid>
      <description>Let us conclude the review by covering the following
Webpage development service In 2022 I have joined the Imperial College Mathematics Society (MathSoc) and Rail and Transport Society (ICRTS) as a webmaster to upgrade their society website. The website has been upgraded from the PHP framework to the user-family React.js framework, and efforts have been made to improve the design of the website. My duties as webmaster were successfully handed over to new committee members, including Chris Boddy (MathSoc) and Madalina Ioana-Sas (ICRTS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Appendix: Clarification for CYF interview, 2022 edition</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/clarification_of_cyf_interview_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/clarification_of_cyf_interview_2022/</guid>
      <description>This is a guidance valid in the academic year of 2021-22. Some policies may be altered for this academic year.
TL;DR:
Clarification for confirmation of faith Interview process The CYF is governed by a committee, supervised by a panel of advisors. The committee is formed by an election under the simple majority system to allow equal representation from different parties in CYF. We believe that CYF committees are elected under the guidance of the same Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Christianity</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/christianity_review_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/christianity_review_2022/</guid>
      <description>TL,DR:
Serving in the Cantonese Youth Fellowship (CYF) Summer in the Chinese Churches in London (CCiL) Imperial College Christian Union (ICCU) Adapting in Oxford: community in St. Ebbes church, morning prayer in University College chapel and Oxford Cantonese Fellowship. Serving in the Cantonese Youth Fellowship Cantonese Youth Fellowship (CYF) is a fellowship in the Chinese Churches in London (CCiL), and has been nurturing many leaders that would later serve CCiL. It has been my priviledge to stay in CYF for four years, and to serve in the CYF committee for my second time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Appendix: Reflection on CYF</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/reflection_on_cyf_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 02:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/reflection_on_cyf_2022/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR:
My reflection for my service as vice-chair of the committee of CYF during the first half of 2022: humbleness, relationships with other members, dealing with complex issues. Further recommendations on diversity of serving, working practice. Clarifications on memberships and elections. I would like to firstly thank all communities who have been continuously praying for my continuous development as a christian. I am extremely delighted for my prayer made during my baptism in 2018 has been heard - that I have continuously grow in my faith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minor Prophets</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/minor-prophets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 17:29:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/minor-prophets/</guid>
      <description>Jonah Day 1: Jonah 1:1-13 Jesus asked Jonah to preach against the great city of Nineveh, but Jonah ran away and boarded a ship at Tarshish.
The wickedness of Nineveh scared Jonah away. Interesting that Jonah asked the sailors to throw him into the sea. Do you think Jonah is a good servant of God? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Bible Study - 06/07</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/act15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 04:53:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/act15/</guid>
      <description>Today we will go over Acts 15, verses 1-35. This passage is about the council at Jerusalem debating issue regarding circumcision. A quick plan would be
introduction (10 minutes): warm-up, key questions the debate of circumcision (5+15 minutes): carefully scrutinise the debates in the Jerusalem council tips of handling conflicts (20 minutes): study again the passage and look at how the churches and leaders deal with conflicts applications (20 minutes) wrapping up (10 minutes) Introduction Warm-up question: Do you think churches would compromise in debates regarding theological matters?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Christianity</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/basic_christianity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 16:53:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/basic_christianity/</guid>
      <description>Some summary and notes from the book Basic Christianity by John Stott.
Chapter 1: The Right Approach God has taken initiatives to reveal Himself through creation, revelation (啟示) and salvation.
God demonstrating Himself God has spoken Natural revelation: demonstrated to everyone through his creation. Special revelation: demonstrated by a group of the &amp;ldquo;special messengers&amp;rdquo; to the &amp;ldquo;special people&amp;rdquo;. We are fortunate to acknowledge this revelation through evangelism. God has acted because observation is what we need (due to our sinful and skeptical nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Devotion</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/sunday-devotion-0805/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 14:25:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/sunday-devotion-0805/</guid>
      <description>We will be reading Matthew 19:16-30, the story of a rich man. If you have time, you may wish to continue reading the parable of the workers in the vineyard in Matthew 20:16, but this will only be covered briefly.
Questions By only just verse 26, can you infer what the verse is about? In verse 17 Jesus said &amp;ldquo;there is only One who is good&amp;rdquo;. Who was the One? Was it the rich man?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Devotion</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/sunday-devotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:37:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/sunday-devotion/</guid>
      <description>Objective This is a trial devotion session to encourage CYF members developing habits of morning devotion. We will be reading 1 John every Sunday before the main service. It would be expanded if there are good outcomes.
Logistics Venue: McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in Hammersmith Broadway Time: 8.30am - 9.15am every Sunday. Content: discussion of prescribed materials and catchup. We will be reading 1 John.
Timetable 16/1 (Samuel) - Chapter 1 What is the word of life (v2)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYF Early Jan Meetings</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/cyf-early-jan-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:38:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/news/posts/cyf-early-jan-meetings/</guid>
      <description>The following is a summary for two meetings of CYF, happening on 30/12/2021 (Thursday) and 6/1/2022 (Wednesday). Both meetings are happening in Zoom.
Committee: Justin (President), Samuel (Vice-President), Vera (Vice-President de-facto, worship and music), Cherry (pastoral), Thomas (secretary), Chung (evangelism and outreach)
Covid Arrangement Many CYF participants caught Covid after the gathering on 26/12/2021 (Sunday), and we have prayed for their recoveries. CYF is turning online. CYF will resume normal no later than February.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
