<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>review on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</title>
    <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in review on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Christianity (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/christianity_review_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/christianity_review_2022/</guid>
      <description>Serving in the Cantonese Youth Fellowship Cantonese Youth Fellowship (CYF) is a fellowship in the Chinese Churches in London (CCiL), and has been nurturing many leaders that would later serve CCiL. It has been my priviledge to stay in CYF for four years, and to serve in the CYF committee for my second time. In particular, I have been extremely touched by reading members testimonies from the Break-me-through camp and baptism of some of the members, as God has demonstrated his power through the life-changing stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Appendix: Reflection on CYF</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/reflection_on_cyf_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 02:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/reflection_on_cyf_2022/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR:
My reflection for my service as vice-chair of the committee of CYF during the first half of 2022: humbleness, relationships with other members, dealing with complex issues. Further recommendations on diversity of serving, working practice. Clarifications on memberships and elections. I would like to firstly thank all communities who have been continuously praying for my continuous development as a christian. I am extremely delighted for my prayer made during my baptism in 2018 has been heard - that I have continuously grow in my faith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Academic Outreach</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/academic_outreach_review_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/academic_outreach_review_2022/</guid>
      <description>TL,DR:
Successful launch of Imperial Wiki Project, require more contributions from members of Imperial College. Teaching assistantship in Oxford on Deep Learning Written an article for Logos Academy Imperial MathsWiki Project My personal highlight on academic outreach would have been (co-)founding Imperial College MathsWiki (MathsWiki) with the collaboration from Imperial Wiki Project (WikiSoc, previously Imperial College ChemWiki), as a spin-off from the society webpage upgrade project for the Imperial College Mathematics Society (MathSoc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review 2022 - Academic</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/academic_review_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/academic_review_2022/</guid>
      <description>TL,DR:
Research project at Imperial on equivalence of non-parametric statistical experiments. Coursework at Imperial on functional analysis, optimisation, asymptotic methods, dynamics of games and mathematical biology. Research project at CDT Mathematics of Random Systems on theories of deep learning The final year at Imperial Research Project The major highlight of the year would be the completion of my final year dissertation with Prof. Alastair Young. The dissertation focuses on the equivalence of three non-parametric statistical experiments, including kernel density estimation, regression on Gaussian white noise and regression on Gaussian sequence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of 2022 - an overview</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/review_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 21:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/review_2022/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is a review of 2022. I will include more details.
Graduation Perhaps the biggest highlight of the year would be my graduation from Imperial College.
Miscellaneous Webpage development service MathSoc and RailSoc Music Thanks the organ scholar for my college to teach me some organ! Pieces learn include hymns and chorales: BWV600 Singing day with John Rutter Further engagement in choirs Further development
Further chorales of Bach Elf Choralvorspieles Travelling Southend Isle of Wight Spain Reading Two trips cancelled, one due to Covid and one due to Visa applications Railway Crossrail opening Barking Riverside First time in crosscountry Conclusion Thanks for reading!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
