<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>miscellaneous on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</title>
    <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/categories/miscellaneous/</link>
    <description>Recent content in miscellaneous on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:09:12 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/categories/miscellaneous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>March Weekly plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mar21-weekly-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:09:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/mar21-weekly-plan/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Week 10 (6-12/3) Academic  Optimisation FYP:  Week 11 (13-19/3) Academic  Advanced Analysis: FYP:  Week 12 (20-26/3): Catch-up Week Week 13 (27/3-2/4): Personal branding week Week 14 (3/4-9/4) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February Weekly plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/feb21-weekly-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:01:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/feb21-weekly-plan/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Week 6 (6-12/2) Academic:  Advanced Analysis: Sobolev Space FYP: Density estimation by block stein estimation  Week 7 (13-19/2): Catch-up Week Academic Christianity  CU Events&#39; Week  Week 8 (20-26/2) Academic  Optimisation: Constrained Optimisation FYP: Review of Generalised Linear Regression: M3S2  Week 9 (27/2-5/3) Academic  Advanced Analysis: FYP: Relationship between GLR and GSM  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January Weekly Plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan21-weekly-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 01:01:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan21-weekly-plan/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Week 3 (16-22/1): FYP catch up 16/1 (Sunday)  Optimisation: Lectures Dynamics of Games Coursework: Documentation of relevant codes  17/1 (Monday)  Dynamics of Games Coursework: Documentation of relevant codes  18/1 (Tuesday)  Dynamics of Games Coursework: Presentation and webpage setup. Optimisation: Arrangement of contribution and class representatives Mathsoc: Spring Launch meeting Miscellaneous Matter: National Insurance Number, Provisional Driving License  19/1 (Wednesday)  M&amp;amp;I Study Group: Kick-off session, preparation for website MathWiki: Review and planning  20/1 (Thursday)  Advanced Analysis: Lecture Dynamics of Games: Exam FYP: Planning, Brown and Low convergence theorem: definition of Le Cam distance, scribing the proof (1 day) Christian Union: Hub Advanced Analysis: Distribuiton Theory Miscellaneous Matter: Draft email to Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jan 8 Meeting Minutes</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:19:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Decision after discussion Bible Study  Resume Sunday devotional breakfast: 1 John Resume daily bible reading:  Minor prophets Thessalonians Jeremiah and Lamentations Titus Philemon Ezekiel    Worship  Best training of musicians are to let them have more experience. Emphasis on communication among leaders and musicians.  Other Activities  Table football Music  Improvement for next time  Agenda too long! I have left my home in a rush so everything is in a mess!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masterplan Kickoff Meeting</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:40:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/jan-8-meeting/</guid>
      <description>The following is the agenda for the kickoff on 8/1/2022 (Saturday). Participants are reminded to take Covid test (LFD/PCR) 48 hours before attending. We are meeting 6pm at the foyer of Gabor Hall.
Three courses  Starter: Tomato soup Main: Spaghetti Carbonara Assorted vegetable Dessert: Ice Cream Snacks are provided  Discussion Lifestyle  regular exercise - how to sustain? designing easier meals  Academic Development  overview of coursework materials - what do you want to achieve?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 11:05:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/vision/</guid>
      <description>The following contents are taken from a discussion with my mother on 6/1/2022 (Thursday).
Basic Principles  Reflect on the expected achievements of plans everyday as a way to keep us going Start brainstorming with big direction, then set up easy (small) targets following the direction. It is easy to get lost: think about the example of Peter walking on the sea, and how Jesus responded when Peter hesitated. (Matthew 14:22-33, Bible) Successful planning involves lots of research and discussions Mind your language Be flexible, &amp;ldquo;be water my friend&amp;rdquo; (Bruce Lee)  Basic elements of a plan  knowledge skill habit (usually 21 days or 49 days) attitude  How to seek advice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Page</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:58:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to masterplan 2022 The masterplan 2022 is an integration of various ambitious plans, outlined for personal development and fulfillment of duties in various communities. The main goal of the plan is to develop a healtheir lifestyle, have major breakthrough in academic development and make contributions to the development of various communities.
Categories  Personal Lifestyle Academic Academic Outreach Christianity Personal Branding  Pushing This is the key phrase of publishing the webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
