<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CYF on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</title>
    <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/categories/cyf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CYF on Samuel&#39;s Masterplan 2022</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 17:29:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/categories/cyf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Minor Prophets</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/minor-prophets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 17:29:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/minor-prophets/</guid>
      <description>Jonah Day 1: Jonah 1:1-13 Jesus asked Jonah to preach against the great city of Nineveh, but Jonah ran away and boarded a ship at Tarshish.
 The wickedness of Nineveh scared Jonah away. Interesting that Jonah asked the sailors to throw him into the sea. Do you think Jonah is a good servant of God?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Christianity</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/basic_christianity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 16:53:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/basic_christianity/</guid>
      <description>Some summary and notes from the book Basic Christianity by John Stott.
Chapter 1: The Right Approach God has taken initiatives to reveal Himself through creation, revelation (啟示) and salvation.
God demonstrating Himself  God has spoken  Natural revelation: demonstrated to everyone through his creation. Special revelation: demonstrated by a group of the &amp;ldquo;special messengers&amp;rdquo; to the &amp;ldquo;special people&amp;rdquo;. We are fortunate to acknowledge this revelation through evangelism.   God has acted because observation is what we need (due to our sinful and skeptical nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYF Operational Guideline</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf_operational_guideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 03:36:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf_operational_guideline/</guid>
      <description>Aims of CYF  Provide a fellowship (for Cantonese-speaking high school and university students in the UK). Explore and develop participants&#39; &amp;ldquo;spiritual gifts&amp;rdquo; in serving God. Evangelise (towards Cantonese-speaking high school and university students in the UK).  Recommended timeline A term spans from 1st July to 30th June in the subsequent year. Before starting of the term, a handover meeting should be held.
Programme Planning  We have members with various experience in faith, so it is difficult to cater all needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYF handover 2022</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf_handover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf_handover/</guid>
      <description>This is my little sharing my experience as a vice chair in CYF. There are a few notes before we start:
 This is a personal sharing, so views towards issues may be heavily biased. I am always open to further discussions in these matters. There are actually two vice-chairs, since Vera has been appointed to share some of my duties, including the member and committee interviews. This sharing is supplemented with reference materials, which are included in this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Devotion</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/sunday-devotion-0805/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 14:25:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/sunday-devotion-0805/</guid>
      <description>We will be reading Matthew 19:16-30, the story of a rich man. If you have time, you may wish to continue reading the parable of the workers in the vineyard in Matthew 20:16, but this will only be covered briefly.
Questions  By only just verse 26, can you infer what the verse is about? In verse 17 Jesus said &amp;ldquo;there is only One who is good&amp;rdquo;. Who was the One?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYF Jan 16 Chit Chat</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-jan-16-chit-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:39:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-jan-16-chit-chat/</guid>
      <description>Quick notes from a discussion with CYF friends during the fellowship on 16/1/2021. I have just finished my Dynamics of Games homework and have been exhausted, so I decided to listen and I enjoy that so much. I am also glad that Yanni share my website to others.
 Jocelyn: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about deadair. (Although &amp;ldquo;introverts are happy if extroverts take over&amp;rdquo;.) Joseph: Go beyond being silent and try to respond to others sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Devotion</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/sunday-devotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:37:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/sunday-devotion/</guid>
      <description>Objective This is a trial devotion session to encourage CYF members developing habits of morning devotion. We will be reading 1 John every Sunday before the main service. It would be expanded if there are good outcomes.
Logistics Venue: McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in Hammersmith Broadway Time: 8.30am - 9.15am every Sunday. Content: discussion of prescribed materials and catchup. We will be reading 1 John.
Timetable 16/1 (Samuel) - Chapter 1  What is the word of life (v2)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYF Early Jan Meetings</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-early-jan-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:38:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/posts/cyf-early-jan-meetings/</guid>
      <description>The following is a summary for two meetings of CYF, happening on 30/12/2021 (Thursday) and 6/1/2022 (Wednesday). Both meetings are happening in Zoom.
Committee: Justin (President), Samuel (Vice-President), Vera (Vice-President de-facto, worship and music), Cherry (pastoral), Thomas (secretary), Chung (evangelism and outreach)
Covid Arrangement  Many CYF participants caught Covid after the gathering on 26/12/2021 (Sunday), and we have prayed for their recoveries. CYF is turning online. CYF will resume normal no later than February.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
