<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Statutory on Samuel Lam&#39;s Blogs</title>
    <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/tags/statutory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statutory on Samuel Lam&#39;s Blogs</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:23:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/tags/statutory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Academic Outreach</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:23:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic-outreach/</guid>
      <description>Promotion of mathematics is divided into three main programmes: Integrated study group and MathWiki, MathSoc engagement and general outreach
MathWiki August Research on network analysis between pages Continuous development Roadmap: something like MIT Official Roadmap Encourage allowing access to overview pages of each course. MathSoc to collect examples of M1R and M2R. MathSoc to liaise with more faculties. Technical development: incorporating LaTeX editors. Can we include the cost of buying domain + running server into annual budget?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Study Plan</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:03:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/academic/</guid>
      <description>My committment July Probability Theory I - limiting theorems Theory of Deep Learning August Probability Theory II - Stochastic processes, discrete time martingale, ergodic theory Random Matrix Theory September Functional Analysis </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christianity</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/christianity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 01:17:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/christianity/</guid>
      <description>There are mainly two ways I am involved in outreaching as a christian - fellowship (Cantonese Youth Fellowship CYF) and Imperial College Christian Union (ICCU). However due to workload I will be gradually reducing my engagement in ICCU.
Cantonese Youth Fellowship As the vice-president of the CYF committee, I am responsible for facilitating President work and coordinating among other committees and participants. During the first term, I organised the freshers&amp;rsquo; events and provided pastoral supports to the participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:46:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>Healthier Lifestyle Regular Exercise Objectives: Using prayer and exercise to boost my energy level at the start of the day. Enjoying sense of achievement after each workout Build partnership by doing workout with friends Contribute to improvement in resilience and singing techniques. Goals: Punctuality: Monday night: Running, chest and leg Tuesday morning: Abs/Cores Wednesday morning: Leg/Chest Thursday morning: Running, Biceps and Triceps Running: &amp;gt; 60 minutes with the speed of 10km/h within 3 months (TBC) Cycling: (TBC) Bicep/Tricep: (TBC) Back: (TBC) Core: (TBC) Chest: (TBC) Abs: (TBC) Leg: (TBC) How to maintain Weekly review with partners (TBC) Healthy Diets Sleeping Time Spritual Growth (Bible Reading) Finance </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Page</title>
      <link>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:58:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuel-chlam.github.io/masterplan-2022/testing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to masterplan 2022 The masterplan 2022 is an integration of various ambitious plans, outlined for personal development and fulfillment of duties in various communities. The main goal of the plan is to develop a healtheir lifestyle, have major breakthrough in academic development and make contributions to the development of various communities.
Categories Personal Lifestyle Academic Academic Outreach Christianity Personal Branding Pushing A GitHub workflow has been setup for pushing the website to GitHub pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
